CHARLES NYABEZE

FOUNDER AND GROWTH SPECIALIST

SUMMARY

Hey there! I am an 18-year-old founder and am currently attending school at Carleton University. I am in the CMO position at my startup and am also a Venture Fellow at RippleX Ventures. I am deeply involved in all things Web3, from NFTs to Social Tokens, and have a natural talent for growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FOUNDER

Agora Labs

2021 - Present

- Raised capital from a fund managed by a16z, Coinbase, and Sequoia Capital
- Built and scaled social media presence by 3000%
- Reached \$500K market cap in 72 hours on DESO Blockchain

FUTURE NORTH

Future North

2021 - 2022

- Creation of assets such as posts, stories, newsletters, and video
- · Created and pushed website designs
- · Lead and advised on projects
- Created creative ways to organize and complete content

COMMUNITY LEAD

BlockPerks

2021 - 2022

- Growing community through Twitter, Instagram, and Discord
- Built and scaled social media presence by 3000%
- · Created and executed growth strategies

CONTACT

705-618-1222



charlesnnyabeze@gmail.com



9 Brian St., Sudbury



github.com/Charles-Nyabeze

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Content Creation
- UI/UX Design
- Copywriting
- React.js
- MySQL
- Bulma/Bootstrap
- GitLabs/Git
- MongoDB
- Cloundinary
- MERN stack
- JavaScript
- Express.js

EDUCATION

2021-Present

• Carleton University Full-Stack Web

2020-2021

- Udemy
- The Complete Web Developer in 2020: Zero to Mastery

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Venture Fellow @ RippleX Fellowship

Lean White Belt Certification - Relamco

Digital Marketing - Google

Blockchain Basics - LinkedIn